question_data = {
    "response_code": 0,
    "results": [
        {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
         "question": "The main character in the &quot;Half-Life&quot; franchise is named Morgan Freeman.",
         "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
         "question": "Tetris is the #1 best-selling video game of all-time.", "correct_answer": "False",
         "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
         "question": "In &quot;Sonic Adventure&quot;, you are able to transform into Super Sonic at will after completing the main story.",
         "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
         "question": "The ultimate phrase used by Pharah from Overwatch is: &quot;Justice rains from above!&quot;",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
         "question": "The PlayStation was originally a joint project between Sega and Sony that was a Sega Genesis with a disc drive.",
         "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
         "question": "In Team Fortress 2, being disguised as a scout or medic results in a speed boost.",
         "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
         "question": "The main playable character of the 2015 RPG &quot;Undertale&quot; is a monster.",
         "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
         "question": "The names of Tom Nook&#039;s cousins in the Animal Crossing franchise are named &quot;Timmy&quot; and &quot;Jimmy&quot;.",
         "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
         "question": "&quot;Metal Gear Solid 3: Snake Eater&quot; was released in 2004.", "correct_answer": "True",
         "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
         "question": "Codemasters is the developer of the Gran Turismo series.", "correct_answer": "False",
         "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]}
